If there is clay on here, what happens is, as you come down here and you start taking the clay off the pot, see if I don't keep cleaning that tool off, all it does is keep going round and round and round.
Sometimes it sticks to your pot, sometimes it doesn't.
So when you get clay on your tool, any tool for that matter, clean it off, set it aside.
So you start with a nice clean tool, so that as you take your tool, touch your piece, remember this is still kind of sticky, your clay trimmings don't transfer from your tool back onto your pot.
You're trying to get it off of your pot.
So we're going to come down in here again, clean some more of that off.
See how you have that all down there?
You have to clean this off.
Sometimes you just get little pieces of clay.
Clean it off, you've got a lot of time.
So you have a nice smoothed out bottom down there.
That's it.